https://www.qualityhydraulics.com/about-us/privacy

Introducing Moematics: Click here to get started with Mobile Equipment Telematics.
Design Assistance
Certified Technical SupportComponent SizingCustom Manifold Assembly DesignCustom Valve AssemblyHydraulics, Pneumatics and System IntegrationHydraulic System Optimization
Custom Products
Component Design & IntegrationCustom Hydraulic Power Unit DesignMachine Control SolutionsMoematics
Business Services
Fluid Contamination Measurement & AnalysisInventory Stocking ProgramMoog Repair Service
Products
Hydraulic
AccumulatorsFlow DividersGear MotorsHigh Pressure Valves & PumpsHydraulic CylindersHydraulic FiltersHydraulic Filter ElementsHydraulic ManifoldsHydraulic Particle CountersHydraulic Pulsation & Surge Control EquipmentHydraulics ReservoirsHydraulic Reservoir AccessoriesHydraulics Power UnitsOil Filter CartsPressure Control ValvesProportional ValvesPumps – Gear, Piston, High PressureServo ValvesStack Valves
CONTROLS/ELECTRIC
Electro-Mechanical ActuatorsElectronic Drives & ControlsHydraulic Joystick ControlsMachine ControllersMeasuring SystemsSensorsTelematics
Pneumatic
Air ValvesFilter-Regulator-LubricatorsIntensifiersNFPA CylindersPneumatic CylindersPneumatic Safety ProductsPressure Gauges
View All
Brands
Argo-HytosASA HydraulikBucher HydraulicsConcentric RockfordDonaldsonDynexElesaGreerHydraForceHydro-LineHydrotechnikKar-TechLDI IndustriesMonnierMoog Inc.MP FiltriMurrelektronik
NasonOEM ControlsParker AccumulatorsRoss ControlsSpan InstrumentsSTW TechnicVickers CylindersVonberg ValveYoung EngineeringYuken
View All
About
About Us
Since 1981, Quality Hydraulics & Pneumatics, Inc. has been known for its depth of expertise in pulsation, surge control, accumulators, hydraulic cartridge valve systems, hydraulic filtration and fine motion control.
Learn More
Our Company
CareersHow To OrderTerms of ServicePrivacy Policy
Blog
All Articles
Accumulators
Controller
Cylinders
Introduction
The site editor takes your right to privacy seriously, and wants you to feel comfortable using this web site. This privacy policy deals with personally-identifiable information (referred to as "data" below) that may be collected by this site. This policy does not apply to other entities that are not owned or controlled by the site editor, nor does it apply to persons that are not employees or agents of the site editor, or that are not under the site editor's control. Please take time to read this site's Terms of use.
1. Collection of data
Registration for an account on this site requires only a valid e-mail address and a user name that has not been chosen already. You are not required to provide any other information if you do not want to. Please be aware that the user name you choose, the e-mail address you provide and any other information you enter may render you personally identifiable, and may possibly be displayed on this web site intentionally (depending on choices you make during the registration process, or depending on the way in which the site is configured) or unintentionally (subsequent to a successful act of intrusion by a third party). As on many web sites, the site editor may also automatically receive general information that is contained in server log files, such as your IP address, and cookie information. Information about how advertising may be served on this site (if it is indeed the site editor's policy to display advertising) is set forth below.
2. Use of data
Registration for an account on this site requires only a valid e-mail address and a user name thaData may be used to customize and improve your user experience on this site. Efforts will be made to prevent your data being made available to third parties unless (i) provided for otherwise in this Privacy Policy; (ii) your consent is obtained, such as when you choose to opt-in or opt-out for the sharing of data; (iii) a service provided on our site requires interaction with a third party, or is provided by a third party, such as an application service provider; (iv) pursuant to legal action or law enforcement; (v) it is found that your use of this site violates the site editor's policy, terms of service, or other usage guidelines, or if it is deemed reasonably necessary by the site editor to protect the site editor's legal rights and/or property; or (vi) this site is purchased by a third party, in which case that third party will be able to use the data in the same manner as set forth in this policy. In the event you choose to use links displayed on this web site to visit other web sites, you are advised to read the privacy policies published on those sites.
3. Advertising
Third-party vendors such as Google and Facebook use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to our web site, and may show our ads on sites across the Internet. These parties typically use non-personally-identifiable or anonymous codes to obtain information about your visits to this site. We may use the non-personally-identifiable information collected for remarketing to advertise our products online. You may opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting Google’s Ads Settings.
4. Minors
The site editor might not allow persons who are aged thirteen or younger to become members of this site. For more information, please contact the site administrator.
5. Editing or deleting your account information
You are provided with the ability to edit the information stored for your user account information during registration, by visiting your user account control panel. You can request that your user account be deleted; to do so, please contact the site administrator. Content or other data that you may have provided, and that is not stored within your user account, such as articles published, may continue to remain on the site at the site editor's discretion, even after your user account is deleted. Please see the site's Terms of use for more information.
6. Changes to this privacy policy
Changes may be made to this policy from time to time. You will be notified of substantial changes to this policy either by through the posting of a prominent announcement on the site, and/or by a mail message sent to the e-mail address you have provided, which is stored within your user settings.
7. No Guarantees
While this privacy policy states standards for maintenance of data, and while efforts will be made to meet the said standards, the site editor is not in a position to guarantee compliance with these standards. There may be factors beyond the site editor's control that may result in disclosure of data. Consequently, the site editor offers no warranties or representations as regards maintenance or non-disclosure of data.
8. Contact information
If you have any questions about this policy or about this web site, please feel free to contact the site administrator.
- Toggle
Contact Us
Leave a Message from a Certified Fluid Specialist
Complete the form below and a representative will contact you beween 7:30 am to 4:30 pm CST M-F.
This form is unavailable.
Get a Quote
Place Order
